/**
 * @type {{
 *  question: string,
 *  answers: [ string, string ] | [ string, string, string ] | [ string, string, string, string ],
 *  correct: number,
 *  time: number
 * }[] }
 */
export const questions = [
        {
            question: " Apple was founded before Microsoft.",
            answers: [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            correct: 1,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: "what is the number system comprised solely of 0 and 1s called?",
            answers: [
                "Base 0",
                "Base 2",
                "Base 3"
            ],
            correct: 1,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: "what does I/O stand for?",
            answers: [
                "internal/ online",
                "input/ output"
            ],
            correct: 1,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: "CLI stands for Command Line Interface.",
            answers: [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            correct: 0,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: " who is responsible for creating the original version of MacOS",
            answers: [
                "Steve Jobs",
                "Steve Wozniak",
                "Bill Gates"
            ],
            correct: 2,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: "What was the original meaning of the term Computer?",
            answers: [
                "An early mechanical calculator",
                "A person who did computations professionally"
            ],
            correct: 1,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: "Steve Wozniak is the co-founder of Apple Computers alongside Steve Jobs.",
            answers: [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            correct: 0,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: "which one is an opening tag?.",
            answers: [
                "<p>",
                "</p>"
            ],
            correct: 0,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: "the color red makes people think of danger or it grabs their attention.",
            answers: [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            correct: 0,
            time: 20
        },
        {
            question: "The tech ladder is a scale of products that change price very little and makes you want to buy the next one up.",
            answers: [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            correct: 0,
            time: 20
        },
    ]